

TECH SKILLS

























WORK EXPERIENCE

Recruitment Consultant

Michael Page | Aug 2019 - Jul 2020

Trade Marketing Analyst

Procter & Gamble | Dec 2016 - May, 2019

Assistant Engineer (CAD design)

General Motors | Mar 2004 - Dec, 2011

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Le Wagon Tokyo - Batch #471

Full Stack Web Development

- 9 week intensive program
- covered basic of Ruby, Software modeling, Database & SQL, Front End, Rails Framework & AirBnB project, Final Project

University of Hawai'i / University of **Arkansas**

HOBBIES



ALEXANDRE VIEIRA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

L 080 7999 2539

in www.linkedin.com/in/alexandre-dev

https://github.com/alex-504

M https://medium.com/@alexandre.batista_15812

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a full stack developer based in Tokyo. I am originally from Brazil where I worked in engineering and the consumer goods industry. While building a lot of my own applications, I have developed a passion for front-end development incorporating JavaScript frameworks such as, React, Vue.js, and Stimulus.

WEB DEVELOPMENT **PROJECTS**

MentorHub

https://www.mentor-hub.app/

Book one-on-one conversations with experienced startup and business mentors that genuinely want to help.

- Features: Book video calls, dashboard manager, chat, User and Mentor Page, endorsement system, meeting preparation.
- Role: Dev Lead
- Tools: Ruby on Rails, JSON, API's, JSON, scraping, CSS, SCSS, HTML5, ES6 JavaScript, Bootstrap, Twilio, SQL, Git, Github

Moovers

https://mooovers.herokuapp.com/

Find a 'moover' nearby end get your shoppings delivered within the same day.

- Features: Geolocation finder, instant booking, chat with driver, schedule date and time to deliver
- Role: Project Manager
- Tools: Rails, Ruby, HTML, JavaScript, Twilio, Mapbox API

Mr. Cocktail

https://brazil-cocktail.herokuapp.com/cocktails

A cocktail recipe organizer.

- Features: Create and edit recipes, view and edit new doses.
- Role: Individual development
- Tools: Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS and JavaScript